<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Deep Sleep</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_mixes">Mixes</string>
    <string name="title_sounds">Sounds</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="mixes">Mixes</string>
    <string name="sleep_sounds">Sleep sounds</string>
    <string name="item_name">Item name</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="go_premium">Go Premium!</string>
    <string name="start_free_trial">Start Free Trial</string>
    <string name="bedtime_reminder">Bedtime Reminder</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="version">Version %s </string>
    <string name="unlock_all_sounds">Unlock\n All Sounds</string>
    <string name="remove_ads">Remove\n Ads</string>
    <string name="_7_day_free_trial">7-day Free Trial</string>
    <string name="try_for_free_7_days">Try for free: 7 days\n After %s%s per year </string>
    <string name="per_month">%s%s / month</string>
    <string name="go_premium_info">This subscription gives you unlimited access to our app content library if you don’t cancel before the trial ends, you will be automatically charged %s%s each year until you cancel. If you choose the monthly subscription, you will be automatically charged %s%s each month until you cancel.</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="details_content">By premium, you can:\n\n
        \u2022 Unlock all sounds\n\n
        \u2022 Remove ads\n\n
        Premium subscription automatically renews unless auto-renew is turned off at least 24-hours before the end of the current period.\n
        You can turn off auto-renew at any time from your Google Play Store account settings but refunds will not be provided for any unused portion of the term.\n
        If you cancel a subscription purchased from an app on Google Plfy, you will not receive a refund for the current billing period, but will continue to receive their subscription content for the remainder of the current billing period, regardless of the cancellation date. The cancellation goes into effect the current billing period has passed.\n
    </string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="reminder_content">Regular bedtime helps form\nhealthy sleep habits.</string>
    <string name="select_reminder_time">Select reminder time</string>
    <string name="repeat">Repeat</string>
    <string name="sunday">S</string>
    <string name="monday">M</string>
    <string name="tuesday">T</string>
    <string name="wednesday">W</string>
    <string name="thursday">T</string>
    <string name="friday">F</string>
    <string name="saturday">S</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.\n\nWe use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.\n\nInterpretation and Definitions\nCollecting and Using Your Personal Data\nDetailed Information on the Processing of Your Personal Data\nGDPR Privacy\nCCPA Privacy\n"Do Not Track" Policy as Required by California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)\nChildren\’s Privacy\nYour California Privacy Rights (California Business and Professions Code Section 22581)\nLinks to Other Websites\nChanges to this Privacy Policy\nContact Us\nInterpretation and Definitions\nInterpretation\nThe words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.\n\nThe following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.\n\nDefinitions\nFor the purposes of this Privacy Policy:\n\nYou means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.\nUnder GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), You can be referred to as the Data Subject or as the User as you are the individual using the Service.\n\nCompany (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to Leap Fitness Group.\nFor the purpose of the GDPR, the Company is the Data Controller.\n\nApplication means the software program provided by the Company downloaded by You on any electronic device, named Sleep Sounds.\nAffiliate means an entity that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with a party, where "control" means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing authority.\nAccount means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.\nService refers to the Application.\nCountry refers to: United States\nService Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.\nFor the purpose of the GDPR, Service Providers are considered Data Processors.\n\nThird-party Social Media Service refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.\nPersonal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.\nFor the purposes for GDPR, Personal Data means any information relating to You such as a name, an identification number, location data, online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity.\n\nFor the purposes of the CCPA, Personal Data means any information that identifies, relates to, describes or is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with You.\n\nDevice means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.\nUsage Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).\nData Controller, for the purposes of the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), refers to the Company as the legal person which alone or jointly with others determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data.\n\nDo Not Track (DNT) is a concept that has been promoted by US regulatory authorities, in particular the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC), for the Internet industry to develop and implement a mechanism for allowing internet users to control the tracking of their online activities across websites.\nBusiness, for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), refers to the Company as the legal entity that collects Consumers\’ personal information and determines the purposes and means of the processing of Consumers\’ personal information, or on behalf of which such information is collected and that alone, or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of consumers\’ personal information, that does business in the State of California.\nConsumer, for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), means a natural person who is a California resident. A resident, as defined in the law, includes (1) every individual who is in the USA for other than a temporary or transitory purpose, and (2) every individual who is domiciled in the USA who is outside the USA for a temporary or transitory purpose.\nSale, for the purpose of the CCPA (California Consumer Privacy Act), means selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring, or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a Consumer\’s Personal information to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.\nCollecting and Using Your Personal Data\nTypes of Data Collected\nPersonal Data\nWhile using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You.\n\nGeneral Information. When you sign up to use the App, we may collect Personal data about you such as:\n\nEmail address\nFirst name and last name\nPhone number\nGender\nPassword or passcode\nUsage Data\nHealth data. When you use the App, you may choose to provide personal information about your health such as:\n\nWeight\nHeight\nBody temperature;\nMenstrual cycle;\nSymptoms;\nOther information about your health (including sexual activities), and related activities.\nUsage Data\nUsage Data is collected automatically when using the Service.\n\nUsage Data may include information such as Your Device\’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.\n\nWhen You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.\n\nWe may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device, below list can provide a non-exclusive list of the contents of Usage Data:\n\nHardware model;\nInformation about operating system and its version;\nScreen size and density;\nLanguage and country;\nUnique device identifiers (e.g. IDFA);\nTime zone;\nDevice mute status (related to reminder function)\nIn order to provide a better user experience, we have integrated data statistics tools in the App, they won\’t collect users\’ health data or privacy data and are only used for CRASH targeting and AB-testing for new features and design， The details are as follows:\n\nDevice information\nScreen Size\nOEM Name\nModel\nDevice system information\nOS Name\nOS Version\nOS Build\nTime Zone\nSystem Language\nCarrier Country\nCarrier Name\nLocation information\nThe right to know about Your Personal Data. You have the right to request and obtain from the Company information regarding the disclosure of the following:\n\nThe categories of Personal Data collected\nThe sources from which the Personal Data was collected\nThe business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling the Personal Data\nCategories of third parties with whom We share Personal Data\nThe specific pieces of Personal Data we collected about You\nThe right to delete Personal Data. You also have the right to request the deletion of Your Personal Data that have been collected in the past 12 months.\nThe right not to be discriminated against. You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising any of Your Consumer\’s rights, including by:\n\nDenying goods or services to You\nCharging different prices or rates for goods or services, including the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties\nProviding a different level or quality of goods or services to You\nSuggesting that You will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.\nExercising Your CCPA Data Protection Rights\nIn order to exercise any of Your rights under the CCPA, and if you are a California resident, You can email or call us or visit our "Do Not Sell My Personal Information" section or web page.\n\nThe Company will disclose and deliver the required information free of charge within 45 days of receiving Your verifiable request. The time period to provide the required information may be extended once by an additional 45 days when reasonable necessary and with prior notice.\n\nDo Not Sell My Personal Information\nWe do not sell personal information. However, the Service Providers we partner with (for example, our advertising partners) may use technology on the Service that "sells" personal information as defined by the CCPA law.\n\nIf you wish to opt out of the use of your personal information for interest-based advertising purposes and these potential sales as defined under CCPA law, you may do so by following the instructions below.\n\nPlease note that any opt out is specific to the browser You use. You may need to opt out on every browser that you use.\n\nWebsite\nYou can opt out of receiving ads that are personalized as served by our Service Providers by following our instructions presented on the Service:\n\nFrom Our "Cookie Consent" notice banner\nOr from Our "CCPA Opt-out" notice banner\nOr from Our "Do Not Sell My Personal Information" notice banner\nOr from Our "Do Not Sell My Personal Information" link\nThe opt out will place a cookie on Your computer that is unique to the browser You use to opt out. If you change browsers or delete the cookies saved by your browser, you will need to opt out again.\n\nMobile Devices\nYour mobile device may give you the ability to opt out of the use of information about the apps you use in order to serve you ads that are targeted to your interests:\n\n"Opt out of Interest-Based Ads" or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" on Android devices\n"Limit Ad Tracking" on iOS devices\nYou can also stop the collection of location information from Your mobile device by changing the preferences on your mobile device.\n\n"Do Not Track" Policy as Required by California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)\nOur Service does not respond to Do Not Track signals.\n\nHowever, some third party websites do keep track of Your browsing activities. If You are visiting such websites, You can set Your preferences in Your web browser to inform websites that You do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable DNT by visiting the preferences or settings page of Your web browser.\n\nChildren\’s Privacy\nOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us.\n\nIf We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from Our servers.\n\nYour California Privacy Rights (California Business and Professions Code Section 22581)\nCalifornia Business and Professions Code section 22581 allow California residents under the age of 18 who are registered users of online sites, services or applications to request and obtain removal of content or information they have publicly posted.\n\nTo request removal of such data, and if you are a California resident, You can contact Us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with Your account.\n\nBe aware that Your request does not guarantee complete or comprehensive removal of content or information posted online and that the law may not permit or require removal in certain circumstances.\n\nLinks to Other Websites\nOur Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party\’s site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.\nWe have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.\nChanges to this Privacy Policy\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.\n\nWe will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "Last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy.\n\nYou are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.\n\nContact Us\nIt should be noted that whether or not to send us your feedback or bug report is a completely voluntary initiative upon your own decision. If you have a concern about your personal data being misused, or if you want further information about our privacy policy and what it means, please feel free to email us at support@leap.app, we will endeavor to provide clear answers to your questions in a timely manner.\n</string>
    <string name="player_title">Player title</string>
    <string name="timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="group_name">Group name</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="current_selection">Current Selection</string>
    <string name="you_can_add_more_sound">You can add more sound</string>
    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>

    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="unlock_for_free">Unlock for Free</string>
    <string name="unlock_free_text">Watch a short video\n to get this premium mix</string>
    <string name="watch_video">Watch video</string>
    <string name="unlock_all">Unlock All Sounds</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="save_custom">Save custom</string>
    <string name="system_volume">System Volume</string>
    <string name="enter_the_name_for_custom">Enter the name for custom</string>
    <string name="text_not_yet_rated">We hope this app is useful for you. If it, does
        would you please give us a 5 stars and a nice review on Google Play, it really helps!</string>
    <string name="advice_rating_text">This is the best\n you can do for us.</string>
    <string name="estimate">Estimate</string>
    <string name="set_timer">Set Timer</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="_00_00">00:00</string>
    <string name="selected">Selected</string>
    <string name="volume_percentage">%d %%</string>
    <string name="custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="_10_minutes">10 minutes</string>
    <string name="oh_no">Oh, no</string>
    <string name="tell_us_what_we_can_improve">Tell us what we can improve?</string>
    <string name="we_like_you">We like you too!</string>
    <string name="thanks_for_feedback">Thanks for the feedback!</string>
    <string name="estimate_on_google_play">Estimate on Google Play</string>
    <string name="upload_image">Upload Image</string>
    <string name="rain_and_piano">Rain and Piano</string>
    <string name="time_format">%01d:%02d:%02d</string>
    <string name="time_format_short">%02d:%02d</string>
    <string name="set_successfully">Set successfully</string>
    <string name="playing">Playing</string>

    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-9075995454638935~7323183568</string>
    <string name="rewarded_id">ca-app-pub-9075995454638935/8444693543</string>
    <string name="licence_key">MIIBIjANBgkqhkiG9w0BAQEFAAOCAQ8AMIIBCgKCAQEArrlHwJoQMDMK/p7Kur87+RSeWlzFdWlyryQny4yw48CnjCQR9y7GcqaDCE2yV5PO9E9wRlUhLylht3f4Ij7wR7GOzEUFzdLI0+jrcWsOawwGzt79FFV6T4jkFe+Y7x95TrmGM2m6cjzc4UugKIcUfr+pVnHoU2tN8TtuFBU/mfhQeK4vvyCsqY/JKksJfwpNVRJ0jEi37AgJyM8j4gKGesvqW8F7sRCOd36WqcrtaodEipL5CDtJWIxn9t58rivZ4HLBFaQHe5o2525cJX8sIMf1FpfX/RQCUJecxrq2pcQNx8xfDA4fb09jvm3uVHVBuO6oxU2Dhq3xa4o5TZSeVwIDAQAB</string>
    <string name="purchase_id_test">android.test.purchased</string>

    <string name="app_test_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
    <string name="interstitial_test_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>
    <string name="congratulations_you_are_lucky">Congratulations,\nyou are lucky!</string>
    <string name="no_need_to_watch_ads_now">No need to watch ads now</string>

</resources>